{
  "extraDescription": "Convert improper fractions to/from mixed fractions",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5\\frac{3}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "23/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{29}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "5 4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{23}{4}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "5 3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3\\frac{3}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "15/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{11}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "2 1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{17}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "3 2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{5}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "1 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{4}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "1 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5\\frac{2}{3}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "17/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{8}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "1 3/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3\\frac{4}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "19/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4\\frac{2}{3}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "14/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{8}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "2 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1\\frac{3}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "8/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{23}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "4 3/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{11}{4}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "2 3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5\\frac{3}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "28/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{11}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "3 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{13}{4}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "3 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{22}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "4 2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2\\frac{1}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "9/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{6}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "1 1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2\\frac{1}{3}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "7/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{19}{4}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "4 3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{5}{4}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "1 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{7}{4}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "1 3/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5\\frac{1}{2}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "11/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{16}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "5 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5\\frac{2}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "27/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{16}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "3 1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2\\frac{1}{2}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "5/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{27}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "5 2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1\\frac{1}{3}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "4/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4\\frac{1}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "17/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{17}{4}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "4 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3\\frac{2}{3}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "11/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5\\frac{4}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "29/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{7}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "1 2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2\\frac{1}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "11/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{5}{2}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "2 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2\\frac{3}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "11/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{7}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "2 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1\\frac{4}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "9/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1\\frac{1}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "6/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{11}{2}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "5 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3\\frac{1}{3}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "10/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{28}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "5 3/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4\\frac{4}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "24/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{14}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "2 4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{18}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "3 3/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3\\frac{1}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "16/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{12}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "2 2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1\\frac{2}{3}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "5/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2\\frac{4}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "14/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{14}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "4 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{17}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "5 2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{10}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "3 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{21}{4}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "5 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{13}{3}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "4 1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4\\frac{3}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "19/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4\\frac{1}{2}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "9/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1\\frac{1}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "5/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{3}{2}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "1 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1\\frac{1}{2}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "3/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3\\frac{2}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "17/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{26}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "5 1/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5\\frac{1}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "21/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{13}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "2 3/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1\\frac{3}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "7/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3\\frac{1}{2}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "7/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2\\frac{2}{3}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "8/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{7}{2}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "3 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3\\frac{3}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "18/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(5\\frac{1}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "26/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(4\\frac{1}{3}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "13/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [3]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{9}{2}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "4 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [2]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(3\\frac{1}{4}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "13/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [4]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(\\dfrac{9}{5}\\) to mixed fraction",
      "answer": "1 4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(2\\frac{3}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "13/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert \\(1\\frac{2}{5}\\) to improper fraction",
      "answer": "7/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["cfr"],
      "expectedDenominators": [5]
    }
  ]
}
